{
    "id": "d81e687de4af4a4693b258955324a884",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "James worked very hard, but he could not win the prize, so please don't bring it ......................",
            "description": "To bring something up is to mention it.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5d2dbaeb6b5347e790b0f193b079bb5c"
        },
        {
            "question": "His liver cancer was brought ............................... by years of drinking.",
            "description": "To bring something on is to cause it to happen. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0ffb77d806f545fc9b0362a11965e00f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call ............................ you this evening if I am free.",
            "description": "To call on somebody is to visit them.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "49b295f49ae9432faadd3951dfc3794c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she was in the last place, her parents cheered her ............................. throughout the race.",
            "description": "To cheer somebody on is to encourage them.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0badf1f7ee741d58abe2e3d08a5c9af"
        },
        {
            "question": "I wanted to tell him that I was getting married, but the chance never came .............................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e64305b562248428b5fdf06286628ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was going to take my kids to the movies, but something came .............................. and I had to cancel.",
            "description": "When things come up, they happen unexpectedly.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c47cb53b6f5e4c56b0813504353b63a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "While I was cleaning the attic, I came .................................. this diary of my grandmother.",
            "description": "To come across something is to find it by chance.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "across",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82cc09c596db40f2a11cb90b38d67917"
        },
        {
            "question": "At last her mother gave .............................. and allowed her to sleep over at her friend's house.",
            "description": "To give in is to surrender in a fight or argument.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b9b3608eec7f408fabd1dcd21af31273"
        },
        {
            "question": "After two weeks of trying to build my own website, I gave .................................... and hired a professional web designer.",
            "description": "To give up is to stop trying.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "07f8d4c14aef47f6acc353da5f41d59c"
        },
        {
            "question": "After leaving university, I tried to stay close to my classmates, but slowly, we grew ............................",
            "description": "To grow apart is to get distant from someone.",
            "answers": [
                "away",
                "up",
                "apart"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db731c99e39245ad91090e3883179901"
        },
        {
            "question": "When we were young we used to hang ............................... in the cafe after work.",
            "description": "To hang out is to spend time with someone casually.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "da458977ab0145d1aaa62582865b8f43"
        },
        {
            "question": "He hung ................................. on me even before I could finish a sentence. I will never call him again.",
            "description": "To hang up on somebody is to end a call before the other person is ready.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1beb86f00654457ebc4789f27df9343b"
        }
    ]
}